const arr = [{"id":0,"info":"2nd-year/reproductive/2017","question":"A 31-year-old female G2P1+0 and a known case of uterine fibroids presented to the outpatient department with pain in the lower abdomen for 5 days. Upon examination, the uterus was tender. Which of the following could cause this presentation?","answers":[{"option":"Abruptio placentae","bool":false},{"option":"Gray degeneration","bool":false},{"option":"Red degeneration","bool":true},{"option":"Ectopic pregnancy","bool":false},{"option":"Ovarian torsion","bool":false}]},{"id":1,"info":"2nd-year/reproductive/2017","question":"An 18-year-old girl is diagnosed with Turner's syndrome. What is the most probable chromosomal makeup in this condition?","answers":[{"option":"46, XY","bool":false},{"option":"46, XX","bool":false},{"option":"46, XXX","bool":false},{"option":"46, XXY","bool":false},{"option":"45, XO","bool":true}]},{"id":2,"info":"2nd-year/reproductive/2017","question":"Which of the following is the most common method for performing tubal ligation?","answers":[{"option":"Amniocentesis","bool":false},{"option":"Hysterosalpingography","bool":false},{"option":"Culdocentesis","bool":false},{"option":"Laproscopic tubal ligation","bool":true},{"option":"Hysteroscopic sterilization","bool":false}]},{"id":3,"info":"2nd-year/reproductive/2017","question":"Which of these genes determine the differentiation of testes?","answers":[{"option":"SHOX","bool":false},{"option":"FGF","bool":false},{"option":"SRY","bool":true},{"option":"WNT-1","bool":false},{"option":"SHH","bool":false}]},{"id":4,"info":"2nd-year/reproductive/2017","question":"Which of the following androgen receptors is found on the stromal cells of the prostate gland?","answers":[{"option":"Estrogen","bool":false},{"option":"Testosterone","bool":false},{"option":"DHT","bool":true},{"option":"Androstenedione","bool":false},{"option":"Cortisol","bool":false}]},{"id":5,"info":"2nd-year/reproductive/2017","question":"If the left uterine tube is removed and the right one's isthmus is contracted, what can happen?","answers":[{"option":"No fertilization or implantation occurs","bool":true},{"option":"Implantation can occur but no fertilization","bool":false},{"option":"Both fertilization and implantation occur","bool":false},{"option":"Fertilization occurs but not implantation","bool":false},{"option":"None of these","bool":false}]},{"id":6,"info":"2nd-year/reproductive/2017","question":"Which of these enzymes converts testosterone to dihydrotestosterone?","answers":[{"option":"Aromatase","bool":false},{"option":"Desmolase","bool":false},{"option":"Phospholipase","bool":false},{"option":"21 B hydroxyalse","bool":false},{"option":"5 alpha reductase","bool":true}]},{"id":7,"info":"2nd-year/reproductive/2017","question":"Which of these muscles contributes to the levator prostate muscle?","answers":[{"option":"Levator ani","bool":true},{"option":"Bulbospongiosus","bool":false},{"option":"Transverse perineal muscle","bool":false},{"option":"Obturator internus","bool":false},{"option":"Ischiocavernosus","bool":false}]},{"id":8,"info":"2nd-year/reproductive/2017","question":"Which of these statements is an odd one out for testosterone?","answers":[{"option":"It regulates male libido","bool":false},{"option":"It causes epiphyseal plate closure","bool":false},{"option":"Dihydrotestosterone is more potent than testosterone","bool":false},{"option":"It is converted to dihydrotestosterone by 5 alpha reductase","bool":false},{"option":"Anabolic synthetic steroids have a shorter half life","bool":true}]},{"id":9,"info":"2nd-year/reproductive/2017","question":"Which of these statements regarding genital glands is incorrect?","answers":[{"option":"Ducts of cowper's glands open into membranous urethra","bool":true},{"option":"Prostatic hyperplasia occurs in the transitional zone","bool":false},{"option":"Seminal vesicles secrete fructose for the sperm","bool":false},{"option":"Seminal vesicles secrete an alkaline fluid","bool":false},{"option":"Bartholin's glands open into the vestibule","bool":false}]},{"id":10,"info":"2nd-year/reproductive/2017","question":"Which of these is an effect of progesterone on the uterine endometrium?","answers":[{"option":"It increases glycogen deposition in the glandular epithelium","bool":true},{"option":"It increases myometrial excitability","bool":false},{"option":"It converts glands from coiled to tubular forms","bool":false},{"option":"It works synergistically with estrogen to increase proliferation","bool":false},{"option":"It causes regression of spiral arteries","bool":false}]},{"id":11,"info":"2nd-year/reproductive/2017","question":"Which of these cells secretes the Mullerian inhibitory factor?","answers":[{"option":"Sertoli cells","bool":true},{"option":"Theca interna cells","bool":false},{"option":"Leydig cells","bool":false},{"option":"Granulosa cells","bool":false},{"option":"Pituicytes","bool":false}]},{"id":12,"info":"2nd-year/reproductive/2017","question":"Which of these cardiovascular changes is observed in pregnancy?","answers":[{"option":"Increase in plasma volume less than the increase in red blood cell mass","bool":false},{"option":"Increase in plasma volume with decreased red blood cell mass","bool":false},{"option":"Increase in plasma volume only","bool":false},{"option":"Decreased plasma volume and red blood cell mass","bool":false},{"option":"Increase in plasma volume more than the increase in red blood cell mass","bool":true}]},{"id":13,"info":"2nd-year/reproductive/2017","question":"Which of these is an immediate precursor to progesterone?","answers":[{"option":"Pregnenolone","bool":true},{"option":"Testosterone","bool":false},{"option":"Cholestrol","bool":false},{"option":"Androstenedione","bool":false},{"option":"Dihydroprogesterone","bool":false}]},{"id":14,"info":"2nd-year/reproductive/2017","question":"What effect does high estrogen level in pregnancy has?","answers":[{"option":"Decrease in the fatty substance of the breasts","bool":false},{"option":"Decreased prolactin secretion","bool":false},{"option":"Prevention of lactation","bool":true},{"option":"Decreased breast growth","bool":false},{"option":"Increased milk secretion","bool":false}]},{"id":15,"info":"2nd-year/reproductive/2017","question":"Which of these statements is incorrect regarding mifepristone?","answers":[{"option":"It is an anti-abortion drug","bool":true},{"option":"It is used orally","bool":false},{"option":"It is typically used in combination with misoprostol","bool":false},{"option":"It is a progesterone antagonist","bool":false},{"option":"It is effective in early pregnancy","bool":false}]},{"id":16,"info":"2nd-year/reproductive/2017","question":"What is the effect of prolactin on menstruation?","answers":[{"option":"It causes heavy menstrual bleeding","bool":false},{"option":"It leads to prolonged luteal phase","bool":false},{"option":"It causes menorrhagia","bool":false},{"option":"It leads to prolonged menstrual cycle","bool":false},{"option":"It causes amenorrhea","bool":true}]},{"id":17,"info":"2nd-year/reproductive/2017","question":"Which of these cells undergo meiosis II?","answers":[{"option":"Secondary spermatocyte","bool":true},{"option":"Germ cell","bool":false},{"option":"Spermatogonia","bool":false},{"option":"Primary spermatocyte","bool":false},{"option":"Spermatid","bool":false}]},{"id":18,"info":"2nd-year/reproductive/2017","question":"What is the difference between prepubertal and pubertal ovarian follicles?","answers":[{"option":"Post puberty, secondary follicles containing stratum granulosum can be found","bool":true},{"option":"Prepubertal follicles contain primary oocytes arrested in metaphase","bool":false},{"option":"Prepubertal follicles contain germ cells","bool":false},{"option":"Prepubertal follicles contain secondary oocyte","bool":false},{"option":"Post puberty, ovarian follicles increase in number","bool":false}]},{"id":19,"info":"2nd-year/reproductive/2017","question":"What are the cornua of sacrum?","answers":[{"option":"Articular processes for the iliac bone","bool":false},{"option":"Median ridge of the sacrum","bool":false},{"option":"Inferior articular extension of fifth sacral vertebra","bool":true},{"option":"Site of attachment of ligamentum flavum","bool":false},{"option":"Foramina through which sacral nerves exit","bool":false}]},{"id":20,"info":"2nd-year/reproductive/2017","question":"Which of these ligaments form the major support of the uterus?","answers":[{"option":"Broad ligament","bool":false},{"option":"Cardinal ligaments","bool":true},{"option":"Sacrospinous ligament","bool":false},{"option":"Uteroovarian ligament","bool":false},{"option":"Round ligament","bool":false}]},{"id":21,"info":"2nd-year/reproductive/2017","question":"What is anorchism?","answers":[{"option":"Absence of testes from scrotal sac","bool":false},{"option":"Large testes","bool":false},{"option":"Fused testes","bool":false},{"option":"Absence of testes","bool":true},{"option":"Small testes","bool":false}]},{"id":22,"info":"2nd-year/reproductive/2017","question":"Which of these is not present in colostrum?","answers":[{"option":"Vitamin K","bool":false},{"option":"IgA immunoglobulin","bool":false},{"option":"Amiodarone","bool":true},{"option":"White blood cells","bool":false},{"option":"Lactoferrin","bool":false}]},{"id":23,"info":"2nd-year/reproductive/2017","question":"Which of these is not a complication of undescended testes?","answers":[{"option":"Germ cell tumors","bool":false},{"option":"Infertility","bool":false},{"option":"Phimosis","bool":true},{"option":"Testicular torsion","bool":false},{"option":"Sertoli cell failure","bool":false}]},{"id":24,"info":"2nd-year/reproductive/2017","question":"Which of these is the major source of human chorionic gonadotropin(HCG) in late pregnancy?","answers":[{"option":"Yolk sac","bool":false},{"option":"Amnion","bool":false},{"option":"Breasts","bool":false},{"option":"Placenta","bool":true},{"option":"Corpus luteum","bool":false}]},{"id":25,"info":"2nd-year/reproductive/2017","question":"High temperature in the testes can lead to which of the following?","answers":[{"option":"High levels of LH hormone","bool":false},{"option":"High levels of inhibin A","bool":false},{"option":"Normal spermatogenesis","bool":false},{"option":"Infertility","bool":true},{"option":"Low testosterone production","bool":false}]},{"id":26,"info":"2nd-year/reproductive/2017","question":"Which of these statements accurately describe seminal vesicles?","answers":[{"option":"Site of sperm maturation","bool":false},{"option":"Site of sperm production","bool":false},{"option":"Copulatory organ","bool":false},{"option":"Accessory sex gland","bool":true},{"option":"Intramuscular glands","bool":false}]},{"id":27,"info":"2nd-year/reproductive/2017","question":"In which of the following locations are peg cells found?","answers":[{"option":"Vagina","bool":false},{"option":"Cervix","bool":false},{"option":"Uterine cavity","bool":false},{"option":"Oviducts","bool":true},{"option":"Ovaries","bool":false}]},{"id":28,"info":"2nd-year/reproductive/2017","question":"Which of these approaches is commonly used for tubal ligation?","answers":[{"option":"Intravaginal","bool":false},{"option":"Open abdominal","bool":false},{"option":"Pharmacologic","bool":false},{"option":"Laparoscopic","bool":true},{"option":"Transrectal","bool":false}]},{"id":29,"info":"2nd-year/reproductive/2017","question":"Which of these is not an effect of estrogen replacement therapy in postmenopausal women?","answers":[{"option":"Breast tenderness","bool":false},{"option":"Reduced osteoporotic fractures","bool":false},{"option":"Hot flashes","bool":true},{"option":"Increased risk of endometrial carcinoma if used alone","bool":false},{"option":"Increased thromboembolic risk","bool":false}]},{"id":30,"info":"2nd-year/reproductive/2017","question":"Which of these is a part of the broad ligament?","answers":[{"option":"Cardinal ligaments","bool":false},{"option":"Pubocervical ligaments","bool":false},{"option":"Mesovarium","bool":true},{"option":"Uterosacral ligaments","bool":false},{"option":"Infundibular ligaments","bool":false}]},{"id":31,"info":"2nd-year/reproductive/2017","question":"Which part of the broad ligament covers the uterine tubes?","answers":[{"option":"Mesovarium","bool":false},{"option":"Cardinal ligaments","bool":false},{"option":"Infundibular ligaments","bool":false},{"option":"Mesosalpinx","bool":true},{"option":"Mesometrium","bool":false}]},{"id":32,"info":"2nd-year/reproductive/2017","question":"In which stage of pregnancy is corpus luteum the main source of progesterone?","answers":[{"option":"1st trimester","bool":true},{"option":"3rd trimester","bool":false},{"option":"None of these","bool":false},{"option":"Throughout pregnancy","bool":false},{"option":"2nd trimester","bool":false}]},{"id":33,"info":"2nd-year/reproductive/2017","question":"Which of these karyotypes reflect Turner's syndrome?","answers":[{"option":"46 XO","bool":false},{"option":"45 XO","bool":true},{"option":"47 XXY","bool":false},{"option":"46 XX","bool":false},{"option":"46 XY","bool":false}]},{"id":34,"info":"2nd-year/reproductive/2017","question":"The act of suckling by the baby and subsequent contraction of myoepithelial cells in the breasts promotes which of the lactational processes?","answers":[{"option":"Mammogenesis","bool":false},{"option":"Involution","bool":false},{"option":"Galactopoesis","bool":false},{"option":"Lactogenesis","bool":false},{"option":"Galactokinesis","bool":true}]},{"id":35,"info":"2nd-year/reproductive/2017","question":"Which of these hormones is responsible for the production of milk?","answers":[{"option":"Estrogen","bool":false},{"option":"Beta hCG","bool":false},{"option":"Prolactin","bool":true},{"option":"Oxytocin","bool":false},{"option":"Progesterone","bool":false}]}]
export default arr